xlsoft.com 2012-10-04

# XLsoft Corporation - Localization, Translation, Consulting Service

_Last Updated: 2003/10/1_  
Your privacy is important to XLsoft. This statement discloses the information practices for XLsoft Web sites, including what type of information is gathered and tracked, how the information is used, and with whom the information is shared.

**Collection of your Personal Information**  
We will ask you when we need information that personally identifies you (personal information) or allows us to contact you. Generally, this information is requested when you are submitting a technical support inquiry, requesting a demo software download, signing up e-mail newsletters, or when purchasing and/or registering XLsoft products. Personal information collected by XLsoft.com often is limited to e-mail address and name, but may include other information when needed to provide a service you requested.

For example: If you choose a service or transaction that requires payment, such as making a purchase in the Shop area of the Web site, we will request personal information necessary for billing and/or shipping, such as: name, address, telephone number, and credit card number.

If you give us personal information about somebody else, such as a spouse or work colleague, we will assume that you have their permission to do so.

**Use of your Personal Information**  
We use your personal information for the following purposes:

  * To ensure our site is relevant to your needs.
  * To deliver services that you request or purchase.
  * To alert you to product upgrades, special offers, updated information and other new services from XLsoft, if you so request.
  * To allow you access to limited-entry areas of our site as appropriate.

We occasionally hire other companies to provide limited services on our behalf, including packaging, mailing and delivering purchases, answering customer questions about products or services, sending postal mail and processing event registration. We will only provide those companies the information they need to deliver the service, and they are prohibited from using that information for any other purpose.

XLsoft may disclose your personal information if required to do so by law or in the good-faith belief that such action is necessary to: (a) conform to the edicts of the law or comply with legal process served on XLsoft or the site; (b) protect and defend the rights or property of XLsoft and its family of Web sites, or (c) act in urgent circumstances to protect the personal safety of XLsoft employees, users of XLsoft products or services, or members of the public.

Your information may be stored and processed in the United States or any other country in which XLsoft or its affiliates, subsidiaries or agents maintain facilities, and by using this site, you consent to any such transfer of information outside of your country. XLsoft abides by the safe harbor framework as set forth by the U.S. Department of Commerce regarding the collection, use, and retention of data from the European Union.

**Control of your Personal Information**  
When you register, or otherwise give us personal information, XLsoft.com will not share that information with third parties without your permission, other than for the limited exceptions already listed. It will only be used for the purposes stated above. By registering your information to XLsoft, you may receive information news about the products and services. If you wish not to receive these services, please unsubscribe from here.

XLsoft.com may send out periodic e-mails informing you of technical service or security issues related to a product or service you requested, or confirming you requested a product or service. You will not be able to choose to unsubscribe to these mailings, as they are considered an essential part of the service you have chosen.

**Security of your Personal Information**  
XLsoft.com is committed to protecting the security of your personal information. We use a variety of security technologies and procedures to help protect your personal information from unauthorized access, use or disclosure. For example, we store the personal information you provide in computer servers with limited access that are located in controlled facilities. When we transmit sensitive information (such as a credit card number) over the internet, we protect it through the use of encryption, such as the Secure Socket Layer (SSL) protocol.

**Use of Cookies**  
XLsoft.com uses cookies in some pages. This information is used to ensure we are providing information and services customers need, and to assist in the collection of the site visitation statistics. It is collected in aggregate form and never linked with your personal information.

**Changes to this Statement**  
XLsoft.com will occasionally update this privacy statement. When we do, we will also revise the "last updated" date at the top of the privacy statement.
